

Ebenezer Temitope Ogidiolu

Relationship Manager

+2349169442847

MQ3/350 Prison Quarters, David Mark Road, Minna

Education

Software Enginering (Backend)

ALX Software Enginering School 2022 - 2023

Higher National Diploma (Computer Science)

Kogi State Polytechnic Lokoja 2011 - 2016

© Courses

Backend Web Dev. (Node JS)

Side-Hustle Internship Sep, 2022 - Oct, 2022

Skills

Target Oriented

Teamwork

Problem Solving

Self-Motivated

Good Time

Management

Decision Making

Interpersonal skills

Ability to Learn Fast

₱ Language

English

Yoruba

Links

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ogidioluebenezer

https://www.github.com/dsoft02

https://www.ebendevlab.com

≪References

References available upon request

About Me

i'm a strategic professional, with experience in customer service, operations and personnel management, organizational development, administration, and relationship management. I have a proven track record of strategically planning, coordinating, and implementing procedures and protocols, which has resulted in significant improvements to processes and quality. My commitment lies in guiding these enhancements towards the successful achievement of company goals.

Work Experience

Oct. 2020 - Aug. 2022 United Bank for Africa Plc | Minna, Niger State, Nigeria

Relationship Officer

- I contributed to the risk asset portfolio as a Relationship officer in the SME sector I was responsible for ensuring the SME customers get the necessary loan facility to aid in their business growth
- I manage key customer business and high networth customers account e.g Alhaji Nadabo Saad Ventures, Seamless Communications, Alhaji Jafaar e.t.c.
- Ensure deposit liability mobilization and account opening
- Ensure effective relationship management with new and existing customers
- Risk Asset appraisal, disbursement and Monitoring
- Optimally exploit new and existing opportunities in the market
- Ensure Zero tolerance for inactive/dormant accounts

Dec. 2019 – Sept. 2020 United Bank for Africa Plc | Minna, Niger State, Nigeria

Customer Service Officer

- Logging and resolution of customer issues and complaints
- Cross selling and promotion of the Bank's product and services to customers.
- Work with customer service manager to ensure proper customer service
- Always provide splendid customer services to customers in a friendly and courteous manner
- Open new bank accounts according to laid down rules and guidelines

Sept. 2017 – Nov. 2019

United Bank for Africa Plc | Anyigba, Kogi state, Nigeria

Bank Teller

- Provides account services to customers by receiving cash deposits and Payment of cash withdrawal on request and cashing of cheques.
- Cross selling of the Bank's product and services, Collection of E-Payment (Remitta, Paydirect, Western Union, Money Gram, e.t.c).
- ATM Custodians Team (loading of cash and basic ATM maintenance).

Jan. 2017 – Aug. 2017

Ametech Global Solution System Ltd | Anyigba Kogi State, Nigeria

Part-Time Software Developer

- Developed Computer Based Test Website for Jamb Students
- Developed A time management software for Churches
- Developed Biometric Attendance software
- Development an Android Gospel Hymnbook App
- Developed An e-commerce / ads listing website